John Hazlewood: Hilo How are you doing?
Chilo: Hi, Mr. Dren.
Chilo: I'm good.
John Hazlewood: Good, good. Yeah, I don't know, I was just having a meeting with,
Chilo: Claudia camera.
John Hazlewood: We just got off, so she'll be joining in a moment.
John Hazlewood: And… I don't know.
Claudia Lopez: here already.
John Hazlewood: Oh, okay.
John Hazlewood: I've got another screen up.
Claudia Lopez: Hey, Chilo.
John Hazlewood: Okay, how's your end?
John Hazlewood: I will… Oh, nice hoodie there. Hoodie and sunglasses. Hoodie and sunglasses.
Ceren: It's not sunglasses, but yeah.
John Hazlewood: Oh.
Ceren: Sudhir.
John Hazlewood: Does it look like sunglasses a little bit? Yeah.
Claudia Lopez: you.
John Hazlewood: Okay.
Ceren: First, come back with sunglasses.
John Hazlewood: You know, back in the day when I was growing up, not that many people seem to wear glasses as they do now. Must be because of looking at screens and stuff.
Ceren: It's not the screens, but the fact that we're always looking close by rather than far away.
Ceren: Now it's a sum cost.
Claudia Lopez: Nice.
Ceren: glasses.
Claudia Lopez: Now she looks cool.
John Hazlewood: Yeah, you need to be in our Sunday meetings like that. That's… Indeed.
Ceren: The sunglasses?
John Hazlewood: Yeah, yeah, that'd be perfect for the podcast.
Ceren: Okay.
John Hazlewood: Okay, I'm gonna… just give me a couple minutes, and I'm gonna be right back while we're waiting for the rest of the gang here.
John Hazlewood: And, yeah, and I did post something…
John Hazlewood: I had a meeting with Claudia a little while ago, but… Talked about Athletics Performance Intelligence.
John Hazlewood: But, yeah, posted in the design team chat. I'll be right back.
Claudia Lopez: Hey. Hey, everybody. Mohamed Cerenchilo.
Ceren: Hello?
mohamed abdelmohsen: A local, yeah.
Chilo: Hello, Claudia, how are you?
Claudia Lopez: Can you repeat that?
Claudia Lopez: What did you say?
Ceren: Lisette, how are you?
Chilo: No, sorry, I said hi, Claudia, I said hi.
Claudia Lopez: No, there's somebody mowing the lawn outside my window, so I can't hear it.
Claudia Lopez: But yes, I'm good.
Claudia Lopez: Zuren, who did the, the tech meeting that's right after this one?
Ceren: Oh… Can you repeat the last part of it? I didn't get the question.
Claudia Lopez: Who's the team on that one in that meeting for the tech meeting? The one that comes right after this one.
Ceren: It's basically everyone.
Ceren: Anyone?
Ceren: No specific team on that.
Claudia Lopez: I will be there today.
Ceren: Okay.
Ceren: It works in a, let's say, similar
Ceren: sent as the Sunday Tech meeting.
Ceren: Just… Let's say with less people usually.
John Hazlewood: Okay, so I know that, serena… Diego… Won't be here.
John Hazlewood: I don't know, did anyone else… Yes, I'm…
Ceren: suits He will not be able to join from the beginning, but he might join later on.
Ceren: Emad said that.
John Hazlewood: Okay.
Ceren: Oops, I didn't get anything from anyone else.
mohamed abdelmohsen: Yes. Abubadoui is not active, no more active with us. So we have Chilo, Claudia, Dina, Diego, Ahmed.
mohamed abdelmohsen: Mary Adipanju Viveka Shidur.
mohamed abdelmohsen: I think I sent them the message.
mohamed abdelmohsen: I think we can start right now.
mohamed abdelmohsen: What do things mean?
Ceren: Yeah, I mean, we can start if they join. They joined from where they came in.
Ceren: One second… Awesome.
Ceren: So, we'll take a minute or two to read this, previous meeting summary, then we will move on.
Ceren: Everyone can see my screen right?
mohamed abdelmohsen: Yes.
John Hazlewood: Yeah. Mohammed, if you also want to send a message to Whitney, I don't know if he might want to join. I think today is his day off.
mohamed abdelmohsen: Okay…
Ceren: Hmm.
Ceren: Everyone is done, we can move on to the tasks.
John Hazlewood: Yeah, I just want to note here that on that one second to the last paragraph, the team also discussed redesigning FloLabs.
John Hazlewood: Our innovations.
John Hazlewood: An Innovation Bootcamp University using the same overall visual direction while keeping the messaging different.
John Hazlewood: Reviews and team testimonials were identified as a priority, with the goal of publishing the first one or two reviews by Friday.
John Hazlewood: So yeah, so I want to make sure we get to that, see where we are with publishing, what that looks like, and… and also, the design, it's not just supposed to… they're supposed to look the same, but they're supposed to look like…
John Hazlewood: The deep mind… Website.
Ceren: Visual direction.
John Hazlewood: Yeah.
Ceren: Not the visual, but direction, so yeah.
John Hazlewood: Yeah, but it doesn't say DeepMind, it just says the same overall visual direction, so I just wanted to make sure that it's…
Ceren: Okay.
John Hazlewood: Maybe.
John Hazlewood: Okay, and…
John Hazlewood: Okay.
Ceren: as well.
John Hazlewood: Yeah.
Ceren: Could we start from that then, since
Ceren: I don't know who was… I think it was…
Ceren: Imad and Tiago, so we can't actually start with that.
Ceren: We can start with the FloBrain V2 wireframes, since that was something that…
Ceren: You guys couldn't check last weekend? Last week?
Ceren: Me too.
Ceren: Claudia and Chino.
Claudia Lopez: For the, wireframes?
Claudia Lopez: We got… I got 3… we got 3 of the screens done. I wasn't able to work on it a whole lot.
Claudia Lopez: But I did get a lot of the details in it.
Claudia Lopez: The rest of the screens, we can copy-paste the side, and then just edit the inside, so we can get through that faster.
Claudia Lopez: I can show what I have, what we have.
Claudia Lopez: And then I wasn't sure, Hiran, if you wanted us to do, I did it in a dark mode.
Ceren: Okay.
Claudia Lopez: I'll never touch it.
Claudia Lopez: I might have changed a couple of things on here.
Claudia Lopez: Let's see.
Claudia Lopez: Dai buddies are over here.
Claudia Lopez: Up here, I put the team activity. It used… it was, activity log. I changed it to team activity. I saw that you said you wanted that on there.
Claudia Lopez: I changed this here from being highlighted in color to just giving.
Claudia Lopez: The navigation, like a blue bar, so right now we're in the leadership and in the dashboard.
Claudia Lopez: Did the… the icons over here, the meetings link, the chat rooms?
Claudia Lopez: And then, right here, we separated the…
Claudia Lopez: The information that you would put, all the green that's actionable, we made green.
Claudia Lopez: you So that was that one. And then that was the E.
Ceren: Can I say something real quick? Can you get close to the teams on the left sidebar? On any of the…
Ceren: frames.
Claudia Lopez: Do it.
Ceren: Text that says FloBrain.
Claudia Lopez: That says FloBrain on music.
Claudia Lopez: Oh, okay.
Claudia Lopez: You said where?
Ceren: Yeah, just, can you get close to it?
Claudia Lopez: Yeah.
Claudia Lopez: So I added that from the regular.
Claudia Lopez: From our regular one.
Claudia Lopez: As examples.
Ceren: The way it's written.
Ceren: There's no…
Claudia Lopez: written.
Ceren: to be a dash.
Claudia Lopez: Got it.
Ceren: I wanted to fix them.
Claudia Lopez: Still, like, up in OB, though, right?
John Hazlewood: Yeah.
Ceren: what's.
Claudia Lopez: A capital B.
John Hazlewood: Yes, uppercase B and uppercase F, and also a mood changer, it's an uppercase C.
Claudia Lopez: Okay, I will make those edits.
Claudia Lopez: And this one was the view interns. I did make a couple of changes on here too.
Claudia Lopez: Added…
Claudia Lopez: tabs. I did have buttons that said Team 1, Team 2, Team 3, but I think that, having tabs is gonna let you Organize it better, if we can do a drag.
Claudia Lopez: To organize what you're looking at.
Claudia Lopez: Right now, it's in all, so when you're on the team, it's gonna pop up so that I know where you are. Right now, up here in the navigation, we're in leadership, and we're in interns.
Ceren: Okay.
Claudia Lopez: And then this one is the View All Teams.
Claudia Lopez: So this have to. We still have to go. I still have to go in here and change right here. Team activity. We gotta add all of this.
Claudia Lopez: Change the blue and the white on here. So…
Claudia Lopez: Those were the ones that we finished. But like I said, the side ones right here.
Claudia Lopez: All of this on the side, and all of this on the side is gonna be just copy-paste. We just gotta go into these ones and update it to look.
Claudia Lopez: Like that, with, like, the buttons, and the text color, and stuff like that.
Claudia Lopez: Harpar was getting it started.
Claudia Lopez: We do have quite a few strings left, though.
Claudia Lopez: And then I was looking at the other versions, and I did take what I could get from them.
Claudia Lopez: Like, I got your little layout here of the meetings.
Claudia Lopez: I think, somebody else had some type of cabs.
Claudia Lopez: But yeah, so that's how far we got on this so far.
Ceren: Okay.
Claudia Lopez: Like I said, I didn't…
Claudia Lopez: work on it a whole lot, because I did have that other task, you guys said, to have all the mini-guides done, and they are.
Claudia Lopez: We are at last.
Ceren: Yeah.
Ceren: Thank you, Parvats.
Claudia Lopez: Yep.
Ceren: Do you have anything to add on this?
Chilo: I'm still working on mine, but please, I have a question.
Chilo: I'm sorry, Claudia, I want to know if… because I know we're using, like, you know, a different, style guide for this, so I want to know if, at some point, you, like, discussed with Jerry concerning the style guide, because I know it's sort of, it's looking quite different.
Claudia Lopez: yet.
Chilo: time.
Claudia Lopez: So, I was talking to her in regards to,
Claudia Lopez: when you said, high definition, I wasn't sure, like, what colors we should be using, or, like, if you had an aesthetic. That's why I just went with the dark mode. But, I did ask Sheila if she thought that maybe we could create a style guide so that we know what to use, or what colors, and what buttons and stuff, because right now.
Claudia Lopez: I mean, right now, for the rest of the screens, we would have to go by this. The buttons, you know, and this stuff like that, but I don't know if you guys…
Claudia Lopez: If it's gonna change at the end anyways, we can just do it like this and just have all the detail, we don't need the style guide.
Ceren: Can I suggest something before the whole, if you didn't like set a specific style guide for this one yet?
Ceren: No. Use the, when you're in the design section on the Figma's right sidebar.
Ceren: On the design section, there's a thing called styles.
Ceren: Open that.
Ceren: There's color and you can use that color. So once you change that color and give it to give the color to something and change it later on, it changes from the whole thing.
Claudia Lopez: All of it.
Ceren: At the same time, rather than doing one, one by one.
Claudia Lopez: Definitely not.
Ceren: Yeah.
Claudia Lopez: So what do you think about this dispute in the Dharma?
Ceren: I mean, most of our stuff is on the dark mode, so…
Claudia Lopez: That's.
Ceren: Woods work.
Claudia Lopez: this.
Ceren: Even the FloBrain that is out right now is dark mode.
John Hazlewood: Claudia, something's wrong with your microphone.
Claudia Lopez: Shall we continue at any time with what we have right now?
John Hazlewood: Something's wrong with your microphone, Claudia.
John Hazlewood: Claudia, something's wrong with your microphone.
Claudia Lopez: Let me just so that I wouldn't get confused and start picking different colors and then also so that
Claudia Lopez: Good morning.
John Hazlewood: Claudia, can you hear us?
Claudia Lopez: Maybe Dina can help us to start that.
mohamed abdelmohsen: Claudia Can you hear us?
Claudia Lopez: What about that?
mohamed abdelmohsen: Can you disconnect your headphone and connect it again?
mohamed abdelmohsen: Try to disconnect it and connect it again, because we don't understand anything.
mohamed abdelmohsen: From what you're saying, Yeah, right.
Claudia Lopez: Now, yeah, I…
mohamed abdelmohsen: Great.
Ceren: us.
Claudia Lopez: My sound was off, sorry. I was saying, do you want us to just continue it in this dark mode, because it's gonna be changed eventually when it's online? Or…
Claudia Lopez: Do you think it's worth us creating a style guide? And I said, maybe Dina can help us.
Ceren: If you're going to, like, continue with the one you have right now, so the design, the style guide can later on
Ceren: Adjusted, you can use the styles, so it's easier to change.
Ceren: But, if you don't have one right now, you can, use the…
Ceren: one that's, like, FloBrain version 1, the one we have for that out. Since that is out, you can use that as well.
Claudia Lopez: Okay.
Ceren: I don't know if you guys changed that into, design system.
Ceren: But yeah.
Claudia Lopez: That was our update.
John Hazlewood: Yeah, on the style guides, and I just wanna…
John Hazlewood: Start to… Hello!
John Hazlewood: Add stuff to our websites, and… With, specifically here for FloStudios.
John Hazlewood: where it's really want to kind of promote it as kind of this is FloStudios team within Flow Studios.
John Hazlewood: creative agency… And… With, building in the open,
John Hazlewood: Similar like what we did with, On CAIPO.
John Hazlewood: We have a link to our documentation that's on Notion.
John Hazlewood: And, as we update it, you know, that link is there, so all of our documentation
John Hazlewood: Will be… you know, on notion anything that everything that we're building in general.
John Hazlewood: We're going to be taking the FloBrain documentation, the architecture, the design that we've been working on over the last year or so.
John Hazlewood: initially started by previous people that aren't here with us, last one, zero, and so there's documentation on the architecture, detailed architecture. Andrew's put together some documentation, but didn't really update that old documentation.
John Hazlewood: Which we have to go back and do, and…
John Hazlewood: And and we'll be posting that documentation on FloBrain website.
John Hazlewood: So anyone that wants to join can see, you know.
John Hazlewood: Whether whether they're a potential intern that wants to join.
John Hazlewood: or… or they're a potential customer. You know, the architecture and the design that we've been working on over the last year or so
John Hazlewood: It's kind of… I mean, it's research, you can find it out there on the internet, what other companies… I mean, I don't think we're really hiding anything.
John Hazlewood: You know, some people would think, man, that's like proprietary stuff. You really want to put that out there. But you know we're not open. We're not taking our source code for FloBrain and providing it as open source. But I think our documentation
John Hazlewood: And how we're… how we're building, and building in the open.
John Hazlewood: So…
John Hazlewood: you know. So we want to start pushing out everything there and then having things updated. And I think that would probably drive a lot of you know, people that are interested in like developers that it might be interested in joining. And they see FloBrain, and that just provides us a lot of credibility and stuff. And
John Hazlewood: So the same with Flow Studios.
John Hazlewood: It's kind of our site, you know, where we want to take
John Hazlewood: what Claudia, what you just showed us, and…
John Hazlewood: You know, any other information that… stuff that we're using, any type of
John Hazlewood: Documentation that we have for the design team, that…
John Hazlewood: you know, kind of add it as a link to FlowStudios, what we're building, what our design studio, and kind of
John Hazlewood: you know, have a link, so I don't… you know, I just wanted to…
John Hazlewood: In general, we'll want to do that with a lot of,
John Hazlewood: You know, the different teams that we're working with, so…
John Hazlewood: Yeah, Jiren, I don't know if… Have a…
John Hazlewood: You know, look at… through all of our documentation and see what we can add and…
John Hazlewood: Kind of have a…
John Hazlewood: task for next version of Float… of FloStudios to add links to whatever documentation that we have for this team.
Ceren: We can try to see what we can do about that.
Ceren: Change.
Ceren: Thank you for showing your work, and… Yeah.
Ceren: Should we get to the next one?
Ceren: Great.
Ceren: Update some backgrounds.
Ceren: Do we have anyone that's more sure?
Ceren: Chilo, did you show your final lost, let's say.
Ceren: All of the Zoom backgrounds you made?
Chilo: Yes, I did.
Ceren: All right then.
Ceren: website website design methods.
Ceren: Claudia and Montina, the, okay, design system thing.
Ceren: You said you were done. Would you want to share anything? Is there anything to,
Claudia Lopez: Yeah, just the rest of us, and thank you, Dina, she provided me all of those things very quickly.
Claudia Lopez: Appreciate that.
Claudia Lopez: So it's just… Like I said, I use her style guides on for it.
Claudia Lopez: They are, they're all done. We've got, I can zoom in a little bit.
Claudia Lopez: Got the Robo and the Tarl.
Claudia Lopez: Float Travel Innovation Bootcamp, FloLab Innovation Group, Mood Changer.
Claudia Lopez: FloStudios, Cosmos, FloLabs International, and Hephaestus
Claudia Lopez: Like I said, they all have the same thing. They have the core colors, the hierarchy, the cards, navigation, and then… The mission, vision, and…
Ceren: Okay, so we will get these and add them as a part of the, let's say… design.
Ceren: onboarding.
Ceren: Or something like that.
Claudia Lopez: Let me export them like it's a PNG, each one.
Ceren: Yeah, I mean, you can do that as well. Sure.
Ceren: Or you can send, you can also send me the, the link, link of it.
Claudia Lopez: Okay.
John Hazlewood: Yeah, and you know, if there's someplace where we can put that again, I mean, as it evolves and we have new sites and it gets updated.
John Hazlewood: how it's going to be managed, and then I think that's another thing that we could put on the FlowStozio site as far as, you know, style guides, stuff like that. I mean, that… for designers, you know, if you're a designer.
John Hazlewood: You know, this stuff is gonna be what's gonna be, you know, interest…
John Hazlewood: You know, interests you, kind of a…
John Hazlewood: It's kind of for a creative agency, you know, that's what the…
John Hazlewood: That's what they have as part of their, you know, knowledge base, let's say, and…
John Hazlewood: So yeah, so all that's good, good stuff.
John Hazlewood: Looks great.
Ceren: So the next thing we have is… How much shared?
John Hazlewood: Dina, did you want to say something?
Ceren: Oh yeah, I didn't see, sorry.
Dina Tarek: Yes, it's okay. As an update for design system,
Dina Tarek: I had to make skills, so I finished the skills for the design system.
Dina Tarek: I have made 15 skills right now, so I can share one of them.
Ceren: So…
Dina Tarek: So there was this.
Ceren: On the design system Figma file, there are 15, but 15th website seems to be FloBrain and it's empty underneath.
Ceren: How did you end up making 15 sales?
Dina Tarek: Yes, we have already FloBrain. For FloBrain, we have two things. Either we're going to make design system for the website itself, or we're going to do it for the dashboard. So which one you want?
Ceren: I mean, in the end, they will be one thing.
Ceren: So we need to have one. But yeah.
Ceren: I mean, the front end is going to be the one doing the final
Ceren: I think so. They can adjust the color based on what we actually give them.
Dina Tarek: Okay, but it's not going to be the same. Yes, it's going to be the same if you're talking about the primary color.
Dina Tarek: But if you are talking about the typography, the typography we're going to use in the website for FloBrain is not the same if you're going to use it for the dashboard itself.
Dina Tarek: So, that's why it's going to be totally different.
Dina Tarek: And when you are designing for Dashboard.
Dina Tarek: You're going to use different guides and different styles.
Dina Tarek: Rather than if you are using it for the website. And right now, for the website, the current website that we have.
Dina Tarek: that is published, it's more related to the first version, the old version of FloBrain, not the previous version, sorry, the recent version of FloBrain.
Dina Tarek: So if you remember the FloBrain and the first version, it was more talk about the AI and the tokens, and it was more about the resources itself.
Dina Tarek: But
Dina Tarek: In the recent versions of FloBrain, it's more talking about,
Dina Tarek: You know, the whole organization, it's a combination between Notion and Discord.
Dina Tarek: And Zoom meetings, so it's totally different.
Dina Tarek: And I'm not sure, are we going later on to have to…
Dina Tarek: make another website, or adding, the other dashboards, in the FloBrain website.
Ceren: As far as I know, we will have…
Ceren: the version 2 on the same website, once it's done.
Ceren: So they will be working on it, the developers will be working on it once we give them the design.
Ceren: Back end is already getting worked on. So yeah.
Dina Tarek: Okay, so the website we have
Dina Tarek: the different version, and the first one is going to talk about the AI tokens and resources, and the other one is going to be the combination of the three programs, right?
Ceren: I'm… I'm not sure about the tokens and… Oh.
Ceren: Sports, sports… I mean, they will all end up being the same. This is the first version, but the…
Ceren: Yeah, will be the thing that's on there.
Dina Tarek: Okay.
Ceren: As far as I know, John Mahomet What do you guys think?
Ceren: Am I seeing something wrong?
Ceren: I couldn't be sure.
mohamed abdelmohsen: No. You're exactly saying what should be done, but I didn't understand your question, Dina, actually.
Dina Tarek: Okay, just… Let me share what I mean.
mohamed abdelmohsen: leaves
mohamed abdelmohsen: And, by the way, witness coming.
mohamed abdelmohsen: You just send me a message. You're gonna show up now.
Ceren: Dina, if you're sharing your screen, we don't see it.
Dina Tarek: Okay, just a second.
mohamed abdelmohsen: Can you repeat your question again, Dina? I'm so sorry. Can you repeat your question again?
Dina Tarek: Okay,
mohamed abdelmohsen: Share the screen.
Dina Tarek: Okay, my question is for the FloBrain website.
Dina Tarek: It was talking about that we have a dashboard for FloBrain.
Dina Tarek: And it's more about the resources that we have, like the tokens of AI, the memory system.
Dina Tarek: Or the management, or, like, integration layer.
Dina Tarek: So it was more about the resources that the company would have.
Dina Tarek: And it's like you are controlling over the resources that you have, like the memory and AI tokens. This was the first version of the FloBrain.
Dina Tarek: And that's what was the website talking about.
Dina Tarek: Then, later on, as an update for FloBrain, we have different versions, and it was more about talking
Dina Tarek: It's going to be, like, a combination of the three, programs as Zoom meeting and Discord.
Dina Tarek: And, Notion.
Dina Tarek: So, still in the FloBrain website, we're still talking about FloBrain as it's the first version, not the recent versions of it.
Dina Tarek: So my question is, even every dashboard that we have for FloBrain, it has totally different colors.
Dina Tarek: The shades even for the Belber color wasn't the same.
Dina Tarek: So, I have to figure out what is going to be the recent, or the more recent, FloBrain version as a dashboard, and if I need to make, a design system for FloBrain as a dashboard, or for the website.
Dina Tarek: Because this… Two different things.
mohamed abdelmohsen: It's a good question, actually. So what we have right now, according to FloBrain version one, the team agreed that they need to have another UI for the upside that we have for what we have right now. So this is a task separate.
mohamed abdelmohsen: The other task that they're talking about right now, which is FloBrain version 2, with all the resources, like Zoom, Notion, Toggl, all of this stuff, and more, and more than that. Like, the AI Buddy is all of those, gonna be for the second version.
mohamed abdelmohsen: For the version, guys, that you make, like Dina, Diego, Jiren, all the versions that you make right now, we agree on all of them. It's not only the UI that we, let's say, disagree, like the functionality of the website, how it's gonna work, but if we're gonna talk about
mohamed abdelmohsen: let's say we need to update this version, because we're gonna use, for example, we're gonna use Dina's version. So, are we gonna use it this way, or it needs more updates about the functionality that we have, and maybe more than what we have right now? So, I think the more focus right now, actually, on the UI of the first version.
mohamed abdelmohsen: Which is… we have it right now on the domain, and for the second version for FloBrain.
mohamed abdelmohsen: I think, they are ready, actually. So, the FloorLine team can use them.
mohamed abdelmohsen: any one of those we can agree on, whatever it's gonna be yours, Dina, Jiren, Claudia, Diego, whoever, but…
mohamed abdelmohsen: The functionality itself is totally complete.
mohamed abdelmohsen: How can we update the versions, like the dashboards, all the information that we have there from the UI standpoint?
mohamed abdelmohsen: We can work on that. But I think what we have right now is… I think it's enough.
mohamed abdelmohsen: So, the front-end team and the back-end team can work. Unless Mr. John has something else to say, but this is how can I see it, and I think this is what's gonna work right now, because, guys, we have, let's say, 4 different UIs using the same functionality for FloBrain version 2.
mohamed abdelmohsen: So, I think they're gonna start work on that. According to the UI, yes, we can make some modification in the future for FloBrain version 2, but, I hope this answers your question, Dina.
John Hazlewood: Yeah, yeah, I don't… we didn't make a decision on, you know, version 2. We had everybody kind of come up with different designs.
John Hazlewood: So we have to kind of keep on working on what that's going to look like.
John Hazlewood: And…
John Hazlewood: you know, and we need to come up with what version 1's gonna look like. What are the features and functionality that are gonna be in version 1?
John Hazlewood: and start… Park.
John Hazlewood: Yeah, we're… do we have a list of features and functionality?
Ceren: We have for version 2, but I didn't see for version 1.
Claudia Lopez: also.
mohamed abdelmohsen: For version one, I… Yeah, go ahead, Claudia.
Claudia Lopez: I'm grabbing from all four versions. I'm looking at them as I'm doing the screen.
Claudia Lopez: Sorry. I'm looking at all four versions as we're making this screen, and I'm trying to grab items from, like, elements or functions from each one that we can put into it, because that's what we were supposed to do, no? Grab pieces from each one to make the one.
mohamed abdelmohsen: Are you talking right now, like, you can see the full, version from…
Claudia Lopez: I'm talking about the prototypes that me, Dina, Diogo.
Claudia Lopez: That we made the different versions. And right now, I'm making the wireframes, and what I'm saying is that I'm using all of the versions, I'm looking at all of them as I'm making the wireframe. We don't have a list of functions and features, so right now I'm just going through it.
Claudia Lopez: in my head, manually, grabbing what I can to fit into the UI.
mohamed abdelmohsen: Okay, so this is version 2.
mohamed abdelmohsen: I totally understand what we're talking about. Like, what we're talking about right now actually is version one.
Claudia Lopez: Okay.
mohamed abdelmohsen: You know, what we have on the domain right now, the FloBrain that we have on the domain right now, what features that we can have it from V2 and add it there? Should we, have the new version, let's say, with time tracking.
mohamed abdelmohsen: Notion… Let's say the AI bodies.
mohamed abdelmohsen: So we're here actually to address these points, like what we should first make to have it with FloBrain V1, which is on the domain right now. So the software team can work on that. So guys, to let you understand what are we talking about?
mohamed abdelmohsen: The software team will not be able to make all the feature once within the website. They needed to have it like stages, stage by stage. Version two that we have right now actually is, let's say, the guide for us.
mohamed abdelmohsen: So, we're gonna take as much as functionality from version 2, add it to version 1, 1x1, 2x2, whatever, but, like, feature by feature.
mohamed abdelmohsen: Right. So, Mr.
Claudia Lopez: I have a question.
mohamed abdelmohsen: Cameron.
John Hazlewood: Well, well, I mean, we have… we have to…
John Hazlewood: We have to understand what the development team.
John Hazlewood: Is… is… is… what's on the books right now
John Hazlewood: For version 1, what does the development team have that they're working on Because that will dictate.
John Hazlewood: how we build the UI.
John Hazlewood: and what it's gonna look like. Not… not… we're gonna build a UI, and then they're gonna… they're gonna build version 1 out of what we give them. They gotta tell us what they're working on, and then…
John Hazlewood: And then we'll come up with
John Hazlewood: That first version, and then as we move forward, we'll add features and functionality or whatever onto that version.
mohamed abdelmohsen: Is that different? Is that different?
Claudia Lopez: Is that different than the phases? Is that different than the phases that we're working in? Like, we're working in a phase one, which is the leadership, and then the phase two, which is going to be another user. Are you guys talking about that, or no?
Claudia Lopez: Never mind.
mohamed abdelmohsen: It's okay. Yeah, guys, I just want to clarify this point.
mohamed abdelmohsen: Right now, what we have, Mr. John, also, with FloBrain, it's just the chat.
mohamed abdelmohsen: So, you can make the chat right now. Only. This is, let's say, the only functionality that we can have right now. So, if you have an account on FloBrain, you can make your chat with it. And we still make some tests for that. Plus, the memory. Like, to save the memory of this person, this user, the prompt, what he did.
mohamed abdelmohsen: And all of this stuff. Like, but what else?
mohamed abdelmohsen: I think they don't have…
mohamed abdelmohsen: They have the ability, actually, to work on that, but they need to have, let's say, the features from us. So if you, Mr. Journey, were talking about, like, we should talk with Indra about, okay, Indra, so what features your team can work on that first?
mohamed abdelmohsen: I think Indra didn't tell us that she just need to like.
mohamed abdelmohsen: Give me feature by feature, and then I can update it, so…
John Hazlewood: They're working on stuff right now, because she has a PRD.
John Hazlewood: That's been created.
mohamed abdelmohsen: Yes, we have the memory.
Ceren: the.
mohamed abdelmohsen: Back in.
John Hazlewood: Yeah, so what's in the next phase? What are they working on that's in the next phase?
John Hazlewood: But they're working on completing them.
mohamed abdelmohsen: They need a UI to work on that with the features that they're gonna work on. They didn't start to work on something new. They work right now within the chat, the memory, and how to connect the chat between the memory and minimize the tokens usage.
mohamed abdelmohsen: No more than that, as far as I know.
John Hazlewood: Well, again, yeah, we need to understand what they're working on, And…
John Hazlewood: I guess we can dictate what they're working on, but we don't know how long it's going to take.
John Hazlewood: I think it's…
Ceren: The last thing I remember of what I talked with Indra was
Ceren: She set up the phases, and that was how the…
Ceren: development team would be working, so this is what… that is the reason why we are following the same phases.
Ceren: Step by step.
Ceren: I get the whole, they will take whatever we create and implement it on the existing version 1 website parts, because, like.
Ceren: version 1.1, 1.2, and stuff like that. That will probably how it will go.
Ceren: Then, once the entire set, let's say, phases are done, then they will call it version 2.
Ceren: That's probably how it will happen, that's… How it works, so…
mohamed abdelmohsen: 6.
Ceren: We already have the phases. The first phase they asked for is the team lead view, because the team lead view also includes the intern view.
Ceren: Which means… We will have both of them by the time they get that.
Ceren: the user and the, let's say, user and supervising user, I guess. Something like that is how it will start. Then the second phase is the tasks, and we have both of them as wireframes right now. Claudia and Chilo are working on that.
Ceren: So once we are done with them, we can give it to them.
mohamed abdelmohsen: Okay.
mohamed abdelmohsen: Now it's more cleared to me.
mohamed abdelmohsen: So, according to that, Mr. John, Indra asked you before to have it featured by… face by face. She don't want to use version 2 once and make it just face by face, so I think Jerim make it more clear right now about the faces that we should deliver to Indra's team.
John Hazlewood: Yeah. Well.
John Hazlewood: And, yeah, I think that would be…
John Hazlewood: Just whatever is in Phase 1, that's what the UI should look like.
John Hazlewood: Just based on that.
John Hazlewood: We also… Maybe once we have that done.
John Hazlewood: I think we want to have, like, what will, once all the phases, I'm not sure how many phases there are before version 2,
John Hazlewood: But what… are those other phases. Instead of doing one phase at a time.
Ceren: John, we have to do it one phase at a time.
Ceren: Otherwise, it will all get, mixed up.
John Hazlewood: Yeah.
Ceren: screen.
Ceren: So, that wouldn't work.
John Hazlewood: Yeah, no, well, what I mean is, like,
John Hazlewood: if we have the final version, what the UI is going to look like, Mmm.
John Hazlewood: If this isn't something that we're launching to the customers, you know, then…
John Hazlewood: And it's gonna be an internal tool.
John Hazlewood: We could use that.
John Hazlewood: UI.
John Hazlewood: And then, the features that don't work…
John Hazlewood: You know, coming soon, or whatever.
John Hazlewood: And then the features that do work, they're working, so at least we're all using it
John Hazlewood: And we see this is what it's going to look like after 2 months, or whatever.
John Hazlewood: And…
John Hazlewood: you know, I don't know, I'd like to kind of look at that option as well as looking just… if it just has the features and functionality that it's gonna have.
John Hazlewood: But, you know, I want to kind of…
John Hazlewood: Know what it's gonna look like, at least, what it's gonna look like at the end.
John Hazlewood: So we're building down that path, and we're not building, like, what's it going to look like with just these features, then what's it going to look like with these features? You know, what's it going to look like after it's built, so then we can start to see, okay, each version, what it's going to look like.
John Hazlewood: Or, the other option, as I mentioned, have that final version with just link… dead links, basically. Say, coming soon, that could be another option.
John Hazlewood: So the first…
Ceren: three phases, like I said, the first one is team lead user, so it will show
Ceren: Supervising and, I guess we can say it like that. Second phase is notion tasks.
Ceren: Third phase is time tracking, and fourth phase is room text chats. So, basically, the second is implementing Notion.
Ceren: Third is implementing Toggl. Fourth is implementing Discord.
Ceren: like futures.
John Hazlewood: Okay, notion features.
John Hazlewood: Not not integrating notion, but integrating notion features.
Ceren: Moving the, like, task… The tasks, basically.
John Hazlewood: Okay, okay, no, I think that sounds good. I had a meeting with Manny earlier.
John Hazlewood: And we kind of went through and talked about.
John Hazlewood: The three things that he's gonna be working on
John Hazlewood: As far as, like, looking at the plugging in the back end, a FloBrain the time tracking.
John Hazlewood: was one.
John Hazlewood: the, rooms… Chat is LifeKit, it's an open source.
John Hazlewood: Also… And then CRM…
John Hazlewood: was another one that we're going to plug in on the back end, so we can get rid of HubSpot and have our own CRM, but also have the CRM plugged into FloBrain.
John Hazlewood: Wu Sheng is in the data team. He's also in the back end and multimodal team.
John Hazlewood: Hmm.
John Hazlewood: So he's gonna him and Wu Shang and and and Manny are gonna be working as buddies along with a couple other people, maybe 2 or 3 other people.
John Hazlewood: Because we want to take these three open source, because the time tracking is also an open source that we're plugging in in our model.
John Hazlewood: Is anything that we're going to develop within FloBrain, From the back end, But… probably, like.
John Hazlewood: Almost everything will be like open source.
John Hazlewood: Things that are already out there that we're gonna plug into the back.
John Hazlewood: Of it.
John Hazlewood: And…
John Hazlewood: So, what we're gonna do is try to work on all 3 of those simultaneously, so we can build a methodology. We have these 3 open source, the time tracking.
John Hazlewood: data, the CRM, And, and, and the video conferencing chats
John Hazlewood: And then kind of work through the process and see how much of that we can even automate.
John Hazlewood: Because if… if FloBrain's future is to have hundreds of
John Hazlewood: different backends, you know, there's a DocuSign open source that we can just send our own agreements from FloBrain, you know, and we don't need to use DocuSign. And we can have that for our customers also. There's so many different things, like, that are open source, that are back
John Hazlewood: You know, very developed, that we can plug in So, anyway…
John Hazlewood: Yeah, I say that because, you know, and Whitney, that CRM, you're in this… you need to be kind of involved in
John Hazlewood: And that is the data team.
John Hazlewood: Right, yeah, Dina?
Dina Tarek: Yes, I have something about FloBrain, if I can share it.
Dina Tarek: Okay.
Dina Tarek: Okay, this is, this is the FloBrain after you sign up,
Dina Tarek: Right now, we can see a home page.
Dina Tarek: And the homepage has a hero section and the features.
Dina Tarek: And everything… As it is a full website.
Dina Tarek: Or if it's, like, landing page for the dashboard.
Dina Tarek: This is how it looks when you, sign up.
Dina Tarek: You can go to the chat, you can go to the dashboard view, But it should be separated.
Dina Tarek: In other words, if we are trying to open… and right now there's no way to sign out, so I cannot show, the view without signing up, so let me open another tab, just a second.
Dina Tarek: What I'm trying to say that, we have to separate between having a website
Dina Tarek: And seeing the dashboard itself.
Dina Tarek: This is totally different views.
Dina Tarek: It's like we are saying, okay, we have a product, and we have a dashboard, and for this dashboard, you can log in, and in this case, you can see the whole dashboard. But right now, it's like…
Dina Tarek: It's the same thing. There's a website, and at the same time, there's a dashboard in the same website. So, let me share the view, when we…
Dina Tarek: Cheryl didn't sign up.
Dina Tarek: So, this is the view when we didn't yet register.
Dina Tarek: We have the home.
Dina Tarek: And we have the website.
Dina Tarek: So, what I want to say is that when we register or sign in.
Dina Tarek: What you have in that, we can, we will not be able to see,
Dina Tarek: The website itself, because… When you go through the process of signing up.
Dina Tarek: And the process of logging in.
Dina Tarek: At that case, we just be able to see the dashboard itself.
Dina Tarek: The whole dashboard.
Dina Tarek: We will not be able to see the website.
Dina Tarek: But right now, it's kind of confusing. Are we right now using the dashboard itself, or we are using the website?
Dina Tarek: It's like there's a confusion between both of them. It should be separated.
Dina Tarek: It's like when… when you are using any mobile application, for instance, and for simplification, and you just have to, sign up and go to another portal or another mobile application, you will not be able to see the website from the beginning.
Dina Tarek: You just are going to see it at the first time, and then after signing in, or downloading the application, or go through the login, then you will be able to see the portal.
Dina Tarek: You will not be able to see the home, page or the website itself.
Dina Tarek: Did anyone get what I mean?
Claudia Lopez: So, you're talking about, like.
Ceren: making.
Claudia Lopez: Kind of like a landing page?
Claudia Lopez: Where they would click and then go into the portal?
Dina Tarek: Yes, it's confusing that we have both of them in one website.
Dina Tarek: Because think of it, when we have the other version of FloBrain, we had just, you go to the dashboard and then you go to the login and sign in and then you just go to the portal itself or the dashboard itself. You don't see the website at that moment.
John Hazlewood: When you, when you, when you, when you go to Chat Gbt on the web, you go to to the Ui, you know, to the dashboard. You don't go to their homepage where you initially went when you registered for Chat Gbt.
Dina Tarek: Yes, that's in case we are going to ChatGPT because we don't need to have a website.
Dina Tarek: All the people already know what is the ChatGPT or Gemini. They don't need another website to tell them what does that product do, or what is the feature of it. But if we are trying to make a new product.
Dina Tarek: We have to have a website, yes, but
Dina Tarek: It's separated from going to the dashboard. We shouldn't be able to see the homepage.
Dina Tarek: When we sign up.
Claudia Lopez: Version 2, we have just the login for the, we have the login for the interns, and then it just takes you to… to it.
Claudia Lopez: In version 2.
Dina Tarek: Yes, you're correct.
Dina Tarek: But,
Dina Tarek: Think of it, you still don't know what is the FloBrain. So how are you going to know what is the FloBrain?
Dina Tarek: You first go to the website.
Dina Tarek: And you see what is the feature, and then you decide to… you want to go to this dashboard.
Dina Tarek: Then you're going through the process of signing up, and then you log in, and then you go to the dashboard itself, or the portal itself.
Claudia Lopez: So make like a landing page pretty much.
Dina Tarek: Yes, kind of, yeah.
Dina Tarek: In that case, you will not be able to see the homepage or the website.
Dina Tarek: Did you get what I mean?
Claudia Lopez: Yes.
Ceren: Hey, this is something to,
Claudia Lopez: That's it.
Ceren: Give intro to as well, I guess, since this is.
Ceren: A bit easier thing to fix, as well as adding a logout button.
Ceren: For the existing Walgreen.
Ceren: Oh… Thank you for sharing that.
Ceren: Something wrong.
Ceren: Next thing to look at, we have… Publisher, new Space Ventures version.
Ceren: It was near completion.
Ceren: Is Rebecca here?
Ceren: Rebecca, are you here?
Rebecca Anzueto: Yes, I'm here.
Ceren: Okay.
Ceren: It says near completion. Is it done?
Rebecca Anzueto: Yes, it's… it's, finished.
Ceren: Okay.
mohamed abdelmohsen: I'm so sorry, Rebecca. Would you please… you sent me a Google Drive folder, and you said, like, you have the full versions updated there.
mohamed abdelmohsen: So, can you let me know, like. Is Zeus version, you make, let's say, updates after I publish the version that you showed me? For example, Kaibu, you sent me, the last week, a version for…
mohamed abdelmohsen: let's say, the latest version that we have right now on the domain. So, did you make updates after that for CAIBO?
mohamed abdelmohsen: For example?
Rebecca Anzueto: from the one that's already published.
mohamed abdelmohsen: Yeah, on the domain right now. Did you make updates for CAIBU?
Rebecca Anzueto: Oh, I don't know which one's published right now.
Rebecca Anzueto: I haven't checked it.
mohamed abdelmohsen: I'm pretty confused.
mohamed abdelmohsen: just for this point, because you send me the whole Google drive with space venture and legal venture. And
mohamed abdelmohsen: CAIBO and And Toral, you made some updates, so…
mohamed abdelmohsen: Is Zeus are the last updates like you made it, let's say, this week or the week before.
mohamed abdelmohsen: Can you check what we have on the domain right now? If you, if you make changes so I can publish that or.
mohamed abdelmohsen: No, I should not publish.
Rebecca Anzueto: Yeah, the the one that I sent you is the the newest version the newest updates from is not is different from the one that's published.
Rebecca Anzueto: It has, like, a different… different images?
mohamed abdelmohsen: Okay, so… So,
Ceren: Can you share your screen and show us what is the last version?
Ceren: Please.
Rebecca Anzueto: Sure.
Ceren: Did you upload the, did you upload it on version 4, V4, basically?
Rebecca Anzueto: Oh, yes, it's on there.
Ceren: Previous version.
Rebecca Anzueto: It's on v five.
Ceren: Okay.
Rebecca Anzueto: Okay.
mohamed abdelmohsen: So you push your code actually on the GitHub, the company GitHub accounts.
Rebecca Anzueto: It was just for Kaipo.
mohamed abdelmohsen: Can you make it for the other versions?
mohamed abdelmohsen: Because.
mohamed abdelmohsen: I know you did a good job, but I'm a little bit confused about what should I publish? Is it the one that we have right now? Because it's not only about your version. I need to add a Google Tag Manager, link this with Google Search Console, some stuff I need to update it.
mohamed abdelmohsen: So… This is…
Rebecca Anzueto: You want me to… Push it on GitHub as a HTML, or do you want me to convert it?
Rebecca Anzueto: to TypeScript.
mohamed abdelmohsen: No, it's okay, just publish as…
mohamed abdelmohsen: add a new folder with, your updates within each GitHub, repo that we have, let's say, for Kaibu. You made… you look there, you find we have 3 versions, just make a new directory, name it V4,
mohamed abdelmohsen: And then I can look. For Space Venture, look at the versions that we have. You're gonna have directory for latest.
mohamed abdelmohsen: V1, V2, make a new directory there, call it V4, for example, or whatever the name is, and push your code there. So I can know, like, this is the last updates, and then we can publish those.
mohamed abdelmohsen: Let's say as a separate domains, and within this meeting, we can talk about like, yeah, open this and compare it with the main domain that we have, which one is best, and then we can use it.
mohamed abdelmohsen: You know?
mohamed abdelmohsen: Plus, I think… I'm not sure about this part, because I think you make this work, let's say, one week ago, one week ago, I think. The last meeting. We agreed here to have, for each version, another page, actually, called Change Look.
mohamed abdelmohsen: And within this page, you need to tell us, in this page, what the changes that you make, actually.
mohamed abdelmohsen: From the separate, the previous version.
mohamed abdelmohsen: I'm pretty sure you didn't do that with the with what we have right now. But
mohamed abdelmohsen: It's not only for you, Rebecca, it's for everyone, guys. Create a new page called Change Log.
mohamed abdelmohsen: Everyone using Claude to make the stuff, and…
mohamed abdelmohsen: change everything. So, with this page, just document what you changed. So, I changed the hero section, like, the title was, let's say, H5, and they made it H1, something like that, so we can understand what was changing.
mohamed abdelmohsen: It's not a simple thing, I know, but we need it. And using Claude.
mohamed abdelmohsen: We can have this.
mohamed abdelmohsen: Maybe it will be a hidden page, you can see a button for that here, or something, so we can make it, but we can use the link.
mohamed abdelmohsen: And we can see… So.
mohamed abdelmohsen: Yeah.
mohamed abdelmohsen: Or maybe you can have it as a button at the header.
mohamed abdelmohsen: called Changelog. When we click on that, we can see and understand. And maybe when we publish that, at the main domain, we just can delete this button, so… and this page. So, it's not a big deal.
mohamed abdelmohsen: Okay, Rebecca, please, for the latest version that you have, please make a new directory with each GitHub repo, and push it there, and let me know. Like, Muhammad, I published that at this directory. V4 at Space Ventures. V10 at Legal Venture. V, whatever, at this. So, we can publish that.
mohamed abdelmohsen: Okay.
Rebecca Anzueto: Okay, yeah.
mohamed abdelmohsen: Thank you.
John Hazlewood: Rebecca, can you look at the CAIPO?
John Hazlewood: website, typo.ai.
John Hazlewood: I think what you showed us is…
John Hazlewood: Same thing that's on the website, unless…
John Hazlewood: Unless we had something similar, and you tweaked…
John Hazlewood: You tweak that, and there's a newer version
John Hazlewood: That's what I think what we wanted to try and understand is… you know.
John Hazlewood: Is what's on the current website right there.
Rebecca Anzueto: I changed the image.
Rebecca Anzueto: This one.
John Hazlewood: Okay, so you do have an update, so… okay, okay, so you changed… okay, so you have a newer version.
Rebecca Anzueto: The video is white.
Rebecca Anzueto: The older one.
Rebecca Anzueto: Yeah, so that's the newest one.
John Hazlewood: Okay, so you have an updated version. Okay, okay, great, and…
John Hazlewood: And did you get all the feedback from, from the CAIPO team.
Rebecca Anzueto: Just, two feedbacks.
Rebecca Anzueto: I'm still waiting on it.
John Hazlewood: Okay, did you message everybody?
Rebecca Anzueto: I'm going to…
John Hazlewood: Okay.
John Hazlewood: Okay, yeah, and if you can…
John Hazlewood: Check with Antoine, we need to get feedback on that, and…
John Hazlewood: But… but, okay, well, I mean, you have a…
John Hazlewood: If you've gotten the… both Jackie and the other person's feedback, has been…
John Hazlewood: you incorporated you. Do you agree with what what their suggestions are? You don't have to incorporate everything that that
John Hazlewood: That, from what the suggestions that are made.
John Hazlewood: You know, but the idea is we're getting feedback from people, and there's gonna be keepers, and there's gonna be some that we won't want to incorporate.
John Hazlewood: Is that the process that you're going through?
Rebecca Anzueto: Yeah, I'm looking through it.
John Hazlewood: Okay, so… so based on the… the two from Jackie and the other one that you got, is there anything else that you need to do?
John Hazlewood: With this new version that you just showed us, that you need more changes that need to be made, that you're gonna…
John Hazlewood: Based on that feedback?
Rebecca Anzueto: Alright, this is something with, the icon.
Rebecca Anzueto: When it's shared.
Rebecca Anzueto: Is Broken or something?
John Hazlewood: Okay, so this is…
John Hazlewood: This is something that doesn't include Jackie's feedback, or the other person that gave you feedback?
John Hazlewood: You're gonna have… there'll be another version with our feedback?
Rebecca Anzueto: Yes.
John Hazlewood: Okay.
Rebecca Anzueto: Did you see, Legal Ventures? Legal Ethics Ventures? Did Serena show that already?
Ceren: organization.
John Hazlewood: terms.
Ceren: Oh, no.
John Hazlewood: Yeah, do you want to show that to us? So, okay, so that is a new version. So, Mohamed, you're gonna update the current version with this new one, and then…
John Hazlewood: We're continuing to get feedback from all the CAIPO, all the IoT team, as far as suggestions for the next version.
Whitney: Is this something that's, standardized? That all the websites have, like, a subdomain that says V1, V2, V3, or do some of them have, a different format?
John Hazlewood: Right now, we're putting…
John Hazlewood: like, a new version, we would… like, this right here, it's a new version, we would put it on a V something, V1, V2, V3. There's others that might be there, because we have different versions, but right now, it's not… what we want to do is…
John Hazlewood: you know, probably do like a V. 1 dot one or V. 1 dot 2, or kind of with…
John Hazlewood: The improved version, and then on the final version, have the version that we've updated, just so we can have some historic context on
John Hazlewood: What we had before.
John Hazlewood: or new versions that people are working on would be published as maybe V2, V3, V4, and then the one that we decide to keep
John Hazlewood: you know.
John Hazlewood: We get rid of all of, you know, all of them, but we're using it basically for staging.
Whitney: Right.
Whitney: So, like… It's always V, though, right? Like, it's a standard format across each.
Whitney: every single website has V followed by a number, because that way, I could track the.
Whitney: The staging websites, to see if
Whitney: for things like broken links, or spelling errors, or core web vitals, or whatever. We want to be tracking SEO content, see how many times keywords are mentioned, things like that. If they all have the same
Whitney: Address, then I could have the, have kind of that.
Whitney: anything with a V in it.
Whitney: As a subdomain, it could kind of be pulled out… yeah, go ahead.
Ceren: The only one that doesn't go with V1, V2, V3, sometimes even V0, is the one that's FloBrain version 2. And since that is already known as version 2, we just gave it with names right now, and…
Ceren: the Like, it was from…
Ceren: The time that everyone was working on the entirety by themselves, so it is given with name and a number.
Ceren: Other than that, they're all version 1, version 2, and stuff like that.
Whitney: Okay, so, like, alright, great. That's what I wanted to know. So it's gonna be, like, a person's name, like, Rebecca FloBrain or, Jaron FloBrain.
Ceren: I'm gonna share the… link where you can find all of them. Actually, that would be easier.
John Hazlewood: Yeah, the issue with that is there's some that are candidates that we're looking at different ones, and we haven't made a decision, so you're gonna be running stuff on the one that, you know, spending time on doing stuff.
John Hazlewood: On ones that might… we might not be using.
John Hazlewood: So, we need to have a process in place Where… The one…
John Hazlewood: You know, because, like, we have completely different designs in some cases that we're looking at.
John Hazlewood: Not just tweaks and fixes.
John Hazlewood: So…
John Hazlewood: But yeah, so I think we need to have a kind of a structure. What's what's the what's the next version?
John Hazlewood: That we're looking at, or we're about to release… or… you know.
John Hazlewood: And then you can run it on that, or, you know, this is the design team, we're just going to take things, we're going to release it, and then once we have a new release, then, you know, maybe you can check it for whatever, and then we can update it again.
John Hazlewood: Because what… the last thing I want to do is, like, slow down the process here on launching sites, because we already have a bunch of sites that we've developed, and
John Hazlewood: We're just sitting… you know, somewhere, and so I've been thinking about how we can
John Hazlewood: you know, create a better process for that. But yeah. Whitney, how does that sound? Just we update the website, the new site we we sends a message.
John Hazlewood: To… to you, to… Run the tools through.
Whitney: Yeah, that works too, that basically fits in with how it works now, and you know, the,
Whitney: The idea with doing it the other way would just be to, like, catch
Whitney: things before they get published to the live version, but it's perfectly fine, I think, to do it that way. And it's all gonna be automatic, so whatever way we're doing it, it's not really gonna take extra time to look at, like, multiple versions. We can just pull up the info for
Whitney: whatever version we want to look at, and whether it's the live version, or V2, or V4, or Candidate, or something else.
John Hazlewood: Okay, okay, that sounds like it'll be easier, and… And,
John Hazlewood: Yeah, and the designers are supposed to be using Lighthouse
John Hazlewood: And I don't know what you're gonna be running on it, what tools you're gonna be running on it afterwards, but as we start to get this down.
John Hazlewood: You know, the… there should be, like, a skill
John Hazlewood: When the designers are creating the website, then it gets run through, so… You know, it's…
John Hazlewood: you know, when they launched their version, all that stuff has been run through AI, and
John Hazlewood: you know, when you… when it comes to the live version, you can just check it, and we should assume, okay, it's going to be done, because it was programmed in AI when they ran it through it to do that stuff.
Whitney: Yeah.
Whitney: Actually, Mohamed showed me the tool is Lighthouse MD, not,
Whitney: Strictly speaking, Lighthouse itself, but it's, like, it gives you a, a feedback on, how to fix, any issues that Lighthouse, Lighthouse runs reveal.
John Hazlewood: Yeah, yeah, and there should be, like, a way to plug that in.
Whitney: Yeah, yeah, there is. It's great. He showed me how to do it. It works very perfectly, smoothly. You can just plug it right into Claude, and it'll, update your website, and I saw how the numbers went from, like, you know, 70, whatever.
Whitney: Right up to 98, and so, it's like magic.
John Hazlewood: Great, great.
John Hazlewood: Okay, Rebecca, back to you.
Rebecca Anzueto: Okay, Serena, change the… the background.
Rebecca Anzueto: Because… It was too dark, so… And… Some of the images.
John Hazlewood: I think that looks great. I think you guys captured the spirit of…
John Hazlewood: what we were trying to capture initially, what Teodoro was trying to capture,
John Hazlewood: The thing that stuck out was the video on.
John Hazlewood: the one of the things that that she had worked on. She attended an online conference. There's a video clip down down below.
John Hazlewood: That should probably go, it seems, a little out of place.
John Hazlewood: Yeah, right there.
Rebecca Anzueto: question?
John Hazlewood: Yeah,
John Hazlewood: Yeah, I, I…
Ceren: Hindi.
John Hazlewood: Thank you.
Ceren: At the end of the page thing, saying recent initiatives, like that's still if you want to keep it anyway.
Ceren: But at the end of the page, at the place it is right now, it looks… It looks weird.
Rebecca Anzueto: Oh, so you want me to move it?
Rebecca Anzueto: Or… remove it?
Ceren: What do you think, John? Do you want it to be on the page or do you want it remote?
John Hazlewood: Yeah, I think it should. you know. You know, it's probably not necessary, because it's actually not a recent initiative. It was probably once over a year ago now.
John Hazlewood: So, yeah, maybe…
John Hazlewood: Yeah, maybe you could just take that off, take off recent initiatives, and just take that that off completely.
John Hazlewood: That box.
Rebecca Anzueto: Oh.
Rebecca Anzueto: Okay.
John Hazlewood: Yeah, so I think that's kind of what stuck out to me, but I'd like to get other people's thoughts.
John Hazlewood: Muhammad, Mina, Claudia.
Ceren: Why is there a dash?
Ceren: In the Yeah.
Ceren: The your legal playground for that. Yes.
Rebecca Anzueto: I'm separating the titles.
Ceren: But they're already separate because they're on the different lines.
Rebecca Anzueto: Hmm.
Ceren: Like, it looks more like it was meant to be a list item, but there was no more lists. At least that's what I understand it as. That's why I'm asking why.
Rebecca Anzueto: Okay, I can remove it.
Whitney: It looks good visually, you know,
Whitney: The black and white, the colors, font, size, everything, the, all the legal imagery.
Whitney: up there, that big part where it says, yes in capital letters, like, if yes, then your journey starts here. That's the only thing I would… I noticed that maybe, it just sounds a little, like.
Whitney: Salesy or something, and maybe people that are looking to become lawyers are…
Whitney: Having, like, more of a serious mentality and some different language might, appeal to them better.
Whitney: Like, if… if this sounds like you, or maybe it doesn't have to be read, I don't know, just.
Whitney: Let me know what you think.
Whitney: I mean, it sounds kind of like an Instagram hustler, kind of like the way they talk, you know?
Whitney: nuts.
John Hazlewood: much.
Whitney: Like a… like a law school.
John Hazlewood: Okay, okay, yeah. Why don't we,
John Hazlewood: Change that from red to just the same color.
John Hazlewood: I think that's a good, good point.
John Hazlewood: And yeah, and I think the point that Juren, that Dash needs to go, it doesn't make sense for it to be there.
John Hazlewood: In fact, I think we talked about, we'd want to remove every dash
John Hazlewood: You know, every dash and everything that… right… hold on, right there, stop right there. Scroll up a little bit.
John Hazlewood: Right there, yeah.
John Hazlewood: So, growing the culture.
John Hazlewood: I don't know, like the line break right before one small decision repeated daily. I mean, that line in front of it, you know.
John Hazlewood: I don't know, when I see that, I kind of think AI.
John Hazlewood: That seems to be a lot of AI-generated stuff does that.
John Hazlewood: And I don't know the value of really having it there.
Ceren: It's mostly used for quotations or comments, I guess, but… No.
Ceren: The whole thing can also be on one line, but that probably wouldn't fit in the box that's
Ceren: Invisible box that it's put on.
Ceren: The text itself.
John Hazlewood: I'm just talking about that line in front of it that's…
Ceren: You know.
John Hazlewood: That.
John Hazlewood: I don't know if you all noticed that with AI generated content.
John Hazlewood: Right.
John Hazlewood: And we just want to make sure that anything.
John Hazlewood: That makes it look AI generated.
John Hazlewood: is excluded.
John Hazlewood: Because it's just… Not worth it.
John Hazlewood: It's not worth someone thinking it was an AI-generated website.
John Hazlewood: And… and so…
John Hazlewood: Okay, well, does anyone else have any thoughts?
John Hazlewood: Sheila says it looks great. Dina.
John Hazlewood: Anybody?
John Hazlewood: Yeah, I think…
Claudia Lopez: Looks good. There's just a couple of little things in there.
John Hazlewood: and and be at the center of the future. That was kind of a line, and I don't know. We need to like. Look at all of these legal venture Ethics Institutes, Venture Institutes.
John Hazlewood: How that's going to… because that's going to be the same on every site.
John Hazlewood: And and so I don't know how we had that on Sports Ventures Institute.
John Hazlewood: or one of the other Legal Ventures Institute sites, but it needs to be consistent.
John Hazlewood: And, yeah, Dina?
Dina Tarek: I have a suggestion about the navigation board. I can see there is
Dina Tarek: a lot of tabs, and I know it's kind of a recommendation from Claude Design.
Dina Tarek: But we can minimize, the tabs.
Dina Tarek: So.
Dina Tarek: Perhaps we can add them, like, as menu,
Dina Tarek: like, drop list from a tab maybe called, About Us. We can add who we are.
Dina Tarek: And, foundation, the team, So, it's much…
Dina Tarek: and categorize them in the navigation board.
Dina Tarek: Also, I can see there is something, called InMotion, and another tab Cold timeline.
Dina Tarek: I'm not totally understand… As a user, what I should see…
Dina Tarek: or what did they refer to. So, this also might be confusing for the user.
Dina Tarek: And it also more recommended that it might be better to have, like, less than five choices.
Dina Tarek: In navigation board.
Dina Tarek: And a lot of designers recommend that we must have a home tab.
Dina Tarek: For navigation bar.
Dina Tarek: Some of people, yes, some of designers say, we already have the logo and we can click on it, but,
Dina Tarek: List of users doesn't know that, so it must be easier for them to have a home tab.
Dina Tarek: Again, yes, you made wonderful work. Thank you. Just I know this is more related to a recommendation from Cloak Design.
Rebecca Anzueto: Thank you.
John Hazlewood: Yeah, Dina on the header.
John Hazlewood: I think what we talked about before is just like the footer. We want to have kind of a standard header.
John Hazlewood: On our websites.
John Hazlewood: that we're going to be using, so… if the agreement is that there should be an About Us, an About…
John Hazlewood: Home.
John Hazlewood: Whatever.
John Hazlewood: It should just be, like, template, you know, it's like, it's automatically created like that, so we don't have…
John Hazlewood: Unless for some reason we want to do one site differently or whatever, but… Does that make sense, Dina?
Dina Tarek: That they all the websites is going to have the foundation and the team and.
Dina Tarek: We already see it before, but I think I didn't see foundation and team before.
Dina Tarek: So.
Dina Tarek: If it's going to be the same for all websites, yes, we can have a template, but it's going to be changing according to the design itself and the website itself.
Dina Tarek: Then we have to think of it that, most commonly there would be different from website to another.
Dina Tarek: But maybe we can, make a template for, like, if there is a home, for sure, about these things, yes.
Dina Tarek: It's going to be in every, website.
John Hazlewood: Yeah, not a template that the about is going to be the same, but just, you know, the navigation bar at the top.
John Hazlewood: Right, and of course, yeah, team…
John Hazlewood: Right now, we're trying to see…
John Hazlewood: There is some plans to have teams, team members on some of these sites.
John Hazlewood: But… We're not… we're not there yet. Something that we need to start working on.
John Hazlewood: Right now, I'm trying to get something of myself that I did a few weeks ago. I was supposed to get something of Whitney, and I need to go back and…
John Hazlewood: Complete that, kind of… I guess I went back and forth so much that it started giving me.
John Hazlewood: The wrong feedback.
John Hazlewood: But.
John Hazlewood: Yeah. So the plan is, I need to put that on the site, probably on the Flow Labs innovations about the founder.
John Hazlewood: And…
John Hazlewood: story. Something like that is what Chat Gbt recommended. And so yeah, I've got a long thing about I I took from 3 different orientation meetings. I took the
John Hazlewood: the part that I talk about my,
John Hazlewood: My entrepreneurial journey and how I started FloLabs and all that stuff.
John Hazlewood: It's probably, like, Yeah, you guys were on those meetings, so it's probably… 20 minutes, 25 minutes.
John Hazlewood: of… now I'm actually sharing also kind of Hephaestus international and and that part
John Hazlewood: And kind of go through some of the gallery stuff.
John Hazlewood: As part of that, and talk about…
John Hazlewood: Ephesus and Talos and stuff. So now it kind of changes it up a little bit with the website, but…
John Hazlewood: Still… so anyway, I… yeah, I'm gonna try and not finish that, so we could add that.
John Hazlewood: get that to Whitney, and then put that, I think, on Flow Labs innovations. And then I think what Chat Gbt suggested is kind of having
John Hazlewood: on each site.
John Hazlewood: You may be… Team that leads back to that page for right now.
John Hazlewood: Or something, I'm not sure.
John Hazlewood: Right.
John Hazlewood: But yeah, once we do that, then we need to start looking at
John Hazlewood: how we get the team members. We used to have team members on a long time ago.
John Hazlewood: And then, kind of, the idea was to have team members, and then alumni for graduates, and have links.
John Hazlewood: Yeah, they're LinkedIn.
John Hazlewood: bios, so… Yeah, that's kind of the… Probably, well, we can move… forward on…
John Hazlewood: You know, on the one… so we have it on one site.
John Hazlewood: And then we can see if we want to do something different on the other sites, or have all the other sites just lead back to the FloLabs Innovations team page.
John Hazlewood: How does that sound, Dina?
Dina Tarek: Okay.
Dina Tarek: We can work on it.
Claudia Lopez: Dina, so, like, would we be able to make a template of the structure of the navigation, and then the content would change according to the website?
Claudia Lopez: But, like, if there's a structure where everything is In the same area.
Claudia Lopez: We could do a template like that.
Claudia Lopez: What do you think?
Dina Tarek: Let me check that, but right now, we have, like, even different shapes and different, visual appearance for each website.
Dina Tarek: It's not even the same, so we can say we're going to have the template that will match all the website. So even if I'm just talking about the spacing or the UI itself.
Dina Tarek: It's still not the same for all the websites.
Dina Tarek: The only thing that I was talking about is how we're organizing the content itself.
Dina Tarek: Like, we must have the Home tab, About Us tab, Internships tab.
Dina Tarek: Until… But let me check and see what I can do about that.
John Hazlewood: Okay, okay.
John Hazlewood: Yeah, and talking… talking about that, footers and…
John Hazlewood: headers and footers. Yeah, I just we just now created
John Hazlewood: a link to athletics, performance, intelligence. We created a a Linkedin profile.
John Hazlewood: So, we'll have to see… the plan moving forward is each… each one of our sites is going to have their own social media, so how do we add that to, you know, like, change those links on the… on the footer? So… We.
John Hazlewood: You know, yeah, so that was just another thing that…
John Hazlewood: Need to kind of change in the future.
Ceren: I get that we want to have…
Ceren: A separate social media for each of them, but we can, at the moment, barely…
Ceren: Do, like, anything that's related to them on the social media pages that exist.
Ceren: that we use.
John Hazlewood: Well, what we're going to do…
John Hazlewood: Is… yeah, depending on what the website is.
John Hazlewood: You know, like, even Athletics Performance Intelligence You know, we're on a…
John Hazlewood: use it as a way to recruit interns for it, sports science interns. We have You know…
John Hazlewood: So I don't know, we're gonna have to try to take and see if there's…
John Hazlewood: content that we have that can be reused, that we're using for FloLabs.
John Hazlewood: And that we can put onto, you know, our other channels, let's say, or the, you know, separate websites.
John Hazlewood: But… Yeah, but we need to have something as far as, like, LinkedIn is really important.
John Hazlewood: When we have a marketing campaign.
John Hazlewood: RoboCollective… we don't have to necessarily have, like, Facebook and have other things right now, but the LinkedIn, or we have a B2B email campaign,
John Hazlewood: So…
John Hazlewood: Yeah, I think it's gonna be better to have rather than have like it links back to Flow Labs innovations.
John Hazlewood: LinkedIn, and then… They've got a…
John Hazlewood: You know, these are our brands, or whatever, and… Oh.
John Hazlewood: Yeah, I don't know, we'll have to try it and see how this works, and…
John Hazlewood: Determine what makes sense in the future.
John Hazlewood: want to deal with different websites, but also the different social media.
John Hazlewood: When you have different social media, and you… and they're active.
John Hazlewood: that has a huge impact on SEO and Llmo. When they know that you have, you know.
John Hazlewood: So…
Ceren: Yeah.
John Hazlewood: Okay.
Ceren: We have 14 more minutes.
Ceren: And.
Ceren: the things… Is this okay?
Ceren: The things we have left are…
Ceren: Okay, wait, this is something we can talk about Dina.
Ceren: Robocollective Assets and Media Cleanup Strapi Migration. Did you get to work on this with Diogo?
Ceren: or without Diego.
Dina Tarek: I was just responsible for finding better assets, like images, and get some images without…
Dina Tarek: Background, because of the light and dark mode.
Dina Tarek: And he was going to update them with Strapi.
Dina Tarek: I didn't get a feedback about stream. I'm still working on the rest of them.
mohamed abdelmohsen: Jermaine, I want to add something here. Diego sent me a message about he makes some updates for Rovo Collective and push it for a branch, so I need to connect this branch with the main domain and make that actually on the main domain.
mohamed abdelmohsen: But I didn't understand, like, what the updates that he did, because we talked before about RoboCollective gonna have a lot of images, and we need to have all of those images into a separate Strapi project, and then we can fetch those images within DoppSub.
mohamed abdelmohsen: So I'm not sure, did he make that or not? Should I wait for him or not? So…
mohamed abdelmohsen: I need to contact with Dave.
Ceren: Mmhm.
mohamed abdelmohsen: Because if I make, let's say, he make the updates.
mohamed abdelmohsen: right now, delete all the images, and have those images on a Strapi project. So, we need to configure the connection between the Strapi and the project.
mohamed abdelmohsen: But if I publish that right now without making this connection, if he add those images onto Strapi, that means if anyone open RoboCollective right now.
mohamed abdelmohsen: He will see nothing from the images, so…
mohamed abdelmohsen: I can make it as another version, but…
mohamed abdelmohsen: I prefer wait to Diego until he explain what he does.
Ceren: No.
mohamed abdelmohsen: If he make the Strapi project. Yeah.
mohamed abdelmohsen: I'm so sorry, Jane, after you're done, I, I need to say something here about the first task.
Ceren: Mr.
mohamed abdelmohsen: John mentioned.
mohamed abdelmohsen: Okay, guys, so let me share my screen.
mohamed abdelmohsen: Can you see my screen, guys?
Ceren: Yes.
mohamed abdelmohsen: Oh, no.
mohamed abdelmohsen: Okay, here is the Strapi project that we created. Actually, it's for all the meetings that we have.
mohamed abdelmohsen: The automation, the backend data, every meeting, every team.
mohamed abdelmohsen: Below's the reviews.
mohamed abdelmohsen: So
mohamed abdelmohsen: This project actually is ready. The next step for that project, it's just to deliver to the market team, the marketing team, so they can just log in here, like this way.
mohamed abdelmohsen: You know, let me look out.
mohamed abdelmohsen: So, I'll provide them the link.
mohamed abdelmohsen: The the email and the password.
mohamed abdelmohsen: Then, click on Login.
mohamed abdelmohsen: After that?
mohamed abdelmohsen: They're gonna come here. Let's say the automation team meeting, so…
mohamed abdelmohsen: They're gonna come here, create new entry, and they need to have the meeting title, the meeting date, the meeting link.
mohamed abdelmohsen: The summary for the meeting?
mohamed abdelmohsen: And the transcription for the meeting itself here.
mohamed abdelmohsen: For all the meetings. For the reviews that Ahmed and Maria work on, they're gonna do the same, come to review, create an entry.
mohamed abdelmohsen: The review title, and the video itself, or the clip, they're gonna click here.
mohamed abdelmohsen: Add it locally, whatever, and their device, and then the review summary.
mohamed abdelmohsen: Or caption, whatever they're gonna make to show. And after they make this, they're gonna click on save. Or publish. And after that.
mohamed abdelmohsen: The front-end team can use this information easily.
mohamed abdelmohsen: and
mohamed abdelmohsen: I'm pretty sure, we can do that also here, actually, within the design team, because I think I need someone to be assigned with me for FloLabs Innovations. So, the Strapi project is ready, we just need to fill this information.
mohamed abdelmohsen: this information, and the marketing team gonna make those information, and then we can use this information. Actually, the link, the Strapi and come for FloLabs innovations.
mohamed abdelmohsen: And we gonna create.
mohamed abdelmohsen: Yeah, focus about all of this stuff. I think we need to update it. I need someone to work with me, actually, to update for Loves Innovation. We need to update this website, guys.
John Hazlewood: We talked about it last week, that didn't we have a task for someone to work on it? It was going to look like DeepMind. That's what we talked about. That was what was on the summary at the beginning of the meeting.
Ceren: You were also supposed to prepare a Messaging for the website, so…
Ceren: The person designing it could work on that.
John Hazlewood: Well, what we wanted to do is just, I don't know.
John Hazlewood: I was thinking just to create the design, but if you want to use the messaging right now from FloLabs International, let's use that, because what Diego did is basically
John Hazlewood: The same text, you know, it's the…
John Hazlewood: I mean, he wrote it… it's written like it was…
John Hazlewood: you know, FloLabs Innovations Group, because it talks about an incubator and experiential learning. So.
mohamed abdelmohsen: So what is the next step here? Like.
mohamed abdelmohsen: The one who gonna work on that, he will not change anything of the text, nothing related to the message, or he gonna copy what we have on FloLabs International, like the messaging itself here.
John Hazlewood: Try to make someone understand.
mohamed abdelmohsen: solution.
John Hazlewood: Copy what's on FloLabs International.
John Hazlewood: Take the same copy, the same text, And use that text.
John Hazlewood: for FloLabs Innovations.
mohamed abdelmohsen: Okay… So, the same way… Do we should have the inner ships there or not?
John Hazlewood: Sure. I mean, we should have them on as many sites as possible. I guess just
John Hazlewood: I mean, I don't… Well… Yeah.
mohamed abdelmohsen: Okay…
John Hazlewood: Yeah, I'm not sure, I'm not sure. I think, like, if we have some on one site.
John Hazlewood: And then… It gets…
John Hazlewood: you know, it gets better SEO if you have some that are on each site that are… if they're not the same, they have to be kind of changed, and then a button back to one place for the rest of them.
mohamed abdelmohsen: I do agree on this point, like, have one source of truth, like, link everything to it, like, this is gonna be the root, everything may be gonna be a branch, so… related to the SEO, if something, like, every… everything come to this website, that means…
mohamed abdelmohsen: We have more ranking when it comes to…
mohamed abdelmohsen: Google engine, or whatever the browser engine gonna use.
mohamed abdelmohsen: So I do agree on that. So I'm not sure about the innerships if we have it here.
mohamed abdelmohsen: But we actually have this as a button. When we click here.
Ceren: It's gonna lead us…
mohamed abdelmohsen: Terms of here.
John Hazlewood: Yeah, yeah, that that was done intentionally to go to to the FloLabs International.
mohamed abdelmohsen: So, Mr. John, I think
mohamed abdelmohsen: We can use Function Labs International, we can use the same message, the same text.
mohamed abdelmohsen: Okay, maybe we can make some manipulation with the Ui itself here with FloLabs innovation. Plus, we're gonna have, let's say, a page here.
mohamed abdelmohsen: I'm not sure about the budget, WhatsApp, what is news, like…
mohamed abdelmohsen: latest from… I'm not sure about the name. Let me have a discussion between me and ChatGPT.
John Hazlewood: I'm sorry, Mohammed. We already decided if you go to DeepMind, go to DeepMind.
John Hazlewood: That's what it's gonna look like. That's gonna be the same structure as What…
John Hazlewood: Our website should look exactly the same.
John Hazlewood: From a visual standpoint.
John Hazlewood: with boxes on the top like that. I went through and I showed you my ChatGPT. It wasn't exactly, you know.
mohamed abdelmohsen: Yes, yes, the version that you create, yeah.
John Hazlewood: Yeah, so… so… so this is what we need to…
John Hazlewood: Once they just get insights and make it just kind of similar, you know, make it exactly like this.
John Hazlewood: you know, make it exactly like this. Use the same color, the same fonts, the same, you know, box sizes, and…
John Hazlewood: And just make sure we have beautiful images for each all of our projects on the top like that. And then you scroll down and you know, it goes to we have latest news. You know, maybe we don't have latest news. I'm not sure.
John Hazlewood: But, you know, if we don't have it, then we don't have it.
John Hazlewood: We need to see… do we use the same stuff, but change the name of something that we do have?
John Hazlewood: And then, you know, as you scroll down.
John Hazlewood: You know, you've got other things that are going across like that. Do we have it? If we don't have it, then we don't have it.
John Hazlewood: And then we have a podcast. We have connecting the dots. So we want to take this and just make it exactly like this and have a screen of, you know, the whole team, you know, and then a link, and then it talks about whatever
John Hazlewood: And then you scroll down…
John Hazlewood: Yeah, and then it's our footer. So, we want to just make it… you know, You know.
mohamed abdelmohsen: Okay, so this gonna be for the homepage.
mohamed abdelmohsen: This is gonna be for the homepage for FloLabs Innovations. Let's imagine we're gonna have the same structure about the projects, at the beginning course like this, and beneath that.
mohamed abdelmohsen: We gonna have.
mohamed abdelmohsen: more…
mohamed abdelmohsen: about us, like, the same tickets that we have with FloLabs Innovations. So, Mr. John, what you ask right now is using the tickets that we have at FloLabs Innovations.
mohamed abdelmohsen: the messaging, the same text, with the UI of DeepMind itself for the cars and all this information for the projects, and for the podcast.
mohamed abdelmohsen: Let's say we can make something like this.
mohamed abdelmohsen: Like, where did it… Yeah, is this this page? So so.
mohamed abdelmohsen: this page, this section. We can have something like that at the homepage, maybe link to, the old tech meeting that we have at…
mohamed abdelmohsen: let's say, on January here, and summary.
mohamed abdelmohsen: And, click button if you want to see the transcript, lead you to another page, another place here, or if you want to read it.
mohamed abdelmohsen: A small summary about what this was about, like, the main topics here.
mohamed abdelmohsen: And at the header, we can have a page like.
mohamed abdelmohsen: the name itself that we need to have the meetings itself, like WhatsApp, or…
mohamed abdelmohsen: leads from us. I'll make my chat between me and ChatGPT and figure out the right name. And then when you click on this, and when you click on this button.
mohamed abdelmohsen: Let's imagine you're gonna click on this button. You're gonna find you a new page, come up, show up. This new page has here, like, to the right, to the right here, you're gonna have something similar to YouTube.
mohamed abdelmohsen: with this meeting, let's say name, and the place for the image for this meeting. Beneath that, another meeting. Beneath that, another meeting. With this dashboard to the right.
mohamed abdelmohsen: And here…
mohamed abdelmohsen: within the rest of the page, you're gonna have the title for this meeting, and you're gonna have a full window for the meeting itself here. Beneath this meeting, you're gonna have a summary. Beneath this summary, you're gonna have, like, if you want to read the transcript, full transcript, click here. And then if you click on this, he can see the whole transcript of the meeting.
mohamed abdelmohsen: What about that?
John Hazlewood: Yeah, and the reason why we want the full transcript is not because anyone's gonna read it.
John Hazlewood: ACO.
mohamed abdelmohsen: yeah.
John Hazlewood: This SEO that… so we need to make sure that when
John Hazlewood: we have the transcript, if it's a pop-up or whatever, just to make sure that it's in line with SEO standards, and it's gonna get, you know, picked up, and integrated properly. So…
John Hazlewood: Yeah, so that's…
John Hazlewood: That would be like… so basically, the podcast, and then it might go to another page that's either connecting the dots, slash connecting the dots, and then with
John Hazlewood: Kind of a podcast page with our, you know, the… The, the, the summary and…
John Hazlewood: the transcription also on the on the reviews.
John Hazlewood: that Maria… And
John Hazlewood: And Nomada working on.
mohamed abdelmohsen: Yes.
John Hazlewood: That will be slash reviews, and those… that's… those need to go kind of the same thing.
John Hazlewood: with with them. I know he has, like they have some 8 min clips of people talking and and stuff. But anyway, we need to. We need to launch that
John Hazlewood: Fairly quickly. What's the status of that reviews? Page Mohammed.
mohamed abdelmohsen: I have the updates also on Strapi, Mr. John, the plate there, for the meetings and the review. You didn't let me share it again?
mohamed abdelmohsen: We are done with this. We have the review here.
mohamed abdelmohsen: as a collection, they're gonna need to create a new like the title and update the clip that they have.
John Hazlewood: Okay, okay, so that's… Okay, okay, and remember, Muhammad, we went through, and I had a meeting with Manny earlier, but…
John Hazlewood: Drappy.
John Hazlewood: And, and, and.
mohamed abdelmohsen: anyway.
John Hazlewood: railway, they can be uploaded into… plugged into ChatGPT or Claude, and you can prompt it, and you can do that stuff within… within our AI. So.
John Hazlewood: Anyway, we need to kind of work on that to see that's going to be much easier for people to just go to, rather than.
mohamed abdelmohsen: Yes. It will be much simpler to make it this way, but I need to try it first if you want me to guide them about that. Guys, I'm old school guy when it comes to Strapi and database. And if anyone from the back end team here, he can say the same.
mohamed abdelmohsen: AI, when it comes to the database, you should care. You can destroy everything. So, yes, but I will make sure I try it, Mr. John, because…
mohamed abdelmohsen: It's gonna take less time.
John Hazlewood: Okay, I know we have another meeting. Dina, you have a question?
Dina Tarek: Yes, may I work on this task for updating the FloLab, application?
mohamed abdelmohsen: join please join rejoin
mohamed abdelmohsen: Okay. Yes, Dina, we can work on that. Please, Jermaine, can you assign me and Dina for this task, so we can give you the updates next week?
John Hazlewood: Well, yeah, the design, though, of the of the new website. So we need another designer, Mohammed, to be her buddy.
John Hazlewood: So…
mohamed abdelmohsen: Okay.
mohamed abdelmohsen: someone else join, I will… my part only to connect the Strapi project.
mohamed abdelmohsen: Do you eye someone else?
Claudia Lopez: And work on the UI.
Claudia Lopez: Okay.
John Hazlewood: Okay, okay, so Claudia volunteered there, so Claudia and Dina can work on the UI. Claudia, don't forget Athletics Performance Intelligence, that's another thing that we looked at, so that's kind of where we're going to do that, because the messaging on Athletics Performance Intelligence is not very.
John Hazlewood: The way it should be, and so I met with Claudia earlier, and she's going to be reworking that.
John Hazlewood: And I don't know what other sites that we're close to finishing or that are sitting there waiting to be published, but maybe, Jaren, maybe we need to go through, maybe the next couple days we can meet and go through whatever, you know, like the V versions and see what's sitting there waiting.
John Hazlewood: and kind of make decisions. But with the legal one that Rebecca showed us, that needs to be plugged onto a version, once she's updated that, and then kind of take a look at that, and then I think that's going to be the one that we go with.
John Hazlewood: From all the versions that we have on there.
mohamed abdelmohsen: Great, Mr. Jean, I just want to add something at last, so we don't be confused, guys. Everyone, have a new version, please push it at a new directory, name it with V5, whatever the number is, and let Jerry, maybe me also, to know. So we know you published a new version there, so we can publish that, deploy it on Vercel.
mohamed abdelmohsen: And second, I'm so sorry, guys, for most of the websites that we have, we're missing
mohamed abdelmohsen: A good point, actually, Yasin mentioned today, about the log itself. If you search for Asthetic Performance Intelligence website right now, you will not see the logo.
mohamed abdelmohsen: Itself, when someone searched for that, and even within the tag.
Ceren: Metadata icon.
mohamed abdelmohsen: Yeah.
Ceren: also.
mohamed abdelmohsen: Yeah, the icon. Please put the logo icon, so the people can see that, and I think it's gonna help. Give us also ranking, within the SEO. I'm so sorry, Mr. John, for interrupting.
mohamed abdelmohsen: Yep.
John Hazlewood: Okay, we we gotta go. Anything else, Sharon.
Ceren: No, there are some stuff left, but that's usual. It's a two-hour meeting, which we used to do at three or four.
Ceren: So, yeah.
Ceren: We can be done.
John Hazlewood: Okay.
John Hazlewood: Okay, great. Thank you, everybody.
John Hazlewood: See you soon!
Ceren: Yeah.
John Hazlewood: Bye.
Ceren: Bye-bye.